Women Against War; Records apap391
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Yahoo Group Correspondence, 2002-2021
  - OWN Women Against War Action, 2001
    - [Moderator Approved] Bethlehem Neighbors for Peace "PeaceNow" Video Series currently has 5 videos available on youtube., 2013 June 27
    - [Moderator Approved] Lynne Stewart says, 'DISAPPOINTED BUT NOT DEVASTATED'-JOIN VIGIL MONDAY, JULY 1, 4-7PM AT FOLEY SQ.,NYC, ride available from Albany, more actions, 2013 June 28
    - please sign the petition, 2013 June 28
    - [Moderator approved} designation on subject heads is retired from the list serve., 2013 June 29
    - Reminder: " SYRIA Through the eyes of those who called it Home", Monday, July 1 at 7 PM, Albany Public Library, 2013 June 30
    - My new film THE KALASHA AND THE CRESCENT by iara lee, 2013 June 30
    - REMINDER: Support PASTORS FOR PEACE Construction Caravan to Cuba, Wednesday July 10th, 5:30 to 8:30 PM, First Presbyterian Church, Albany, 2013 June 30
    - march to Rore the Fourth, 2013 June 30
    - [Moderator Approved] Video! Hunger striker Diane Wilson after 57 days of hunger striking crossed over the White House Fence., 2013 July 1
    - [Moderator Approved] " Journey For Justice" Needs a place to stay in Guilderland, or Altamont for three walkers on the night of Saturday, July 13th, 2013 July 3
    - [Moderator Approved] Help Needed, 2013 July 5
    - [Moderator Approved] Two row wampum reminder, 2013 July 5
    - [Moderator Approved] Medea Benjamin, Founder of Code Pink, 2013 July 6
    - "Close Gitmo It's Hell on Earth!" Demonstration, Wednesday, July 10, 4pm to 5pm Wolf Road and Central Avenue, Colonie;Followed by Friendshipment Potluck, 5:30 to 8:30 PM, 2013 July 7
    - The Journey for Justice walk needs your driving support, 2013 July 7
    - What do you know about Hebron? Fundraising for a documentary., 2013 July 8
    - A Video invitation to the 2013 Kateri Tekakwitha Interfaith Peace Conference [August 16 and 17, Fonda NY] in 2:15 minutes., 2013 July 9
    - Fwd: reminder: rally for Aref appeal FRIDAY, July 12; Journey for Justice Begins, 2013 July 10
    - [Fwd: Pot luck Summer Evening Get Together to Celebrate " Journey for Justice" Walk Day One], 2013 July 12
    - Stop the War: No Arms to Syria Vigil - Monday July 15, 5 PM to 6 PM Delmar, 2013 July 12
    - Hospitality Needed [Fwd: Updates on Two Row Wampum Renewal Campaign], 2013 July 12
    - Medea Benjamin will speak in the Capital District next Sat, July 20, 10:30 AM, Troy Public Library, 2013 July 13
    - What do Noam Chomsky and Martin Sheen have in common? [Updated and easier to read version of "Ghost Town -- The Hebron Story", 2013 July 13
    - Hear Medea Benjamin in the region in and near the Capital District July 16th through July 28th details below., 2013 July 14
    - Please follow the "Journey for Justice" on Lynne Jackson's blog. Link provided to Lynne's daily updates between Friday, July 12th and Tuesday, July 23rd, 2013 July 14
    - Requ for support drivers for the Walk for Justice, 2013 July 15
    - Medea Benjamin interviewed today, 7/16, on WAMC by newscaster Brian Shields, 2013 July 16
    - Re: A REQU FROM LYNNE JACKSON, 2013 July 16
    - updates on Journey for Justice, 2013 July 18
    - Justice for Trayvon Martin - Demonstrate, Saturday, 2013 July 18
    - Accountability for Drone Strikes - Please Sign!, 2013 July 19
    - last call for handwritten signatures for Yassin Aref petition, 2013 July 20
    - Wednesday, July 24th - Close Gitmo, Stop the torture, Release the cleared prisoners!, 2013 July 20
    - A REMINDER ABOUT THE "JOURNEY FOR JUSTICE" PRESS CONFERENCE IN BINGHAMTON ON TUESDAY, 2013 July 21
    - What do Noam Chomsky and Martin Sheen have in common?, 2013 July 21
    - Capital District Two Row Wampum Events Coming Right Up!], 2013 July 22
    - Medea Benjamin to speak about "Patriarchy, Imperialism and Drone Warfare", at the Social Justice Center, 33 Central Avenue, Thursday, July 25, from 6 to 8 PM, 2013 July 22
    - Guantanamo prot continues in Albany, Wednesday, July 24th Noon to 1 PM, Federal Courthouse, Albany, 2013 July 23
    - House Action Wednesday. 7/24: NSA spying, Syria - Bug Your Rep! Send the editable letter below or even better call him/her., 2013 July 23
    - Fw: Trial Closing Arguments Thu, Actions Fri & Sat!, 2013 July 23
    - [Fwd: Two Row Full Events Schedule], 2013 July 24
    - Martha Hennessy and Dorothy Day - 2013 Kateri Peace Conference. Friday, August 16 and Saturday August 17, Fonda NY, 2013 July 25
    - I've published a blog article about civil rights lawyer, Lynne Stewart and the need for her immediate compassionate release. Some things that YOU can do., 2013 July 27
    - 2 peace events commemorating Hiroshima, and call for disarmament-- Sunday, August 4th Program and potluck, Central Park, Schenectady, 4 PM, "Hiroshima" Reading, Tuesday, August 6th, 11 am, Townsend Park, Albany, 2013 July 28
    - Witness Against Torture Action Thursday, 8/1 In Saratoga Springs, 11:30 am to 1 PM, Across from Saratoga Race Course, 2013 July 28
    - Veterans will end fasts on Sunday, August 4 at Albany mosque, 2013 July 28
    - [undergroundrailroad] Dont Miss Out - Youn g Abolitionist Open House this Thursday, Augu st 1st, 11 am to 1 PM, exhibit of art and vi deo projects by teens, 2013 July 30
    - Reminder: Turkish Cultural Center's Interfaith Ramadan Dinner, Interfaith Center at University at Albany, Friday, August 2nd, 7:30 PM, 2013 July 31
    - Masjid As-Salam and Elliott Adams Invite you to...., 2013 July 31
    - VETERANS WILL END 80-DAY FAST ON AUGUST 4 AT ALBANY MOSQUE, 2013 August 1
    - Solidarity Action w/ Elliot Adams & Tarak Kauff for Breaking the Fast, 2013 August 1
    - COMING TO YOUR INBOX - SOME COMPELLING REASONS TO ATTEND THE FONDA PEACE CONFERENCE, 2013 August 1
    - MODERATE -- Ghost - Town - The Hebron Story, 2013 August 2
    - Ray McGovern - The 2013 Kateri Peace Conference, 2013 August 3
    - Iran demonstration 8/14/13 at Empire State Plaza fival, noon to 1 p.m., 2013 August 5
    - Indiegogo Campaign to End Drone Strikes by f unding a new full length documentary "Unmanne d: Americas Drone Wars", 2013 August 6
    - Legal Update - Good News from John Amidon about his 8/5 court hearing for previous Hancock Prots: Charges reduced to a violation from more serious charge of "criminal tresspass", 2013 August 6
    - Your Voice is Needed: National Religious Call-In Day this Wednesday, 8/7, to CA governor, Jerry Brown on behalf of the prisoners on hunger strike, 2013 August 6
    - Young Adult internship: IFOR 2013 Fellowship School call for applications -- Deadline, 8/22/13, 2013 August 6
    - Reminder about the Kateri Tekakwitha Peace Conference on Friday, August 16th and Saturday, August 17th. Still time to get information and register., 2013 August 7
    - Understanding Your Right to Vote, short documentary "The Barber of Birmingham" Wednesday, August 14, 6 PM Albany Public Library, main branch, Q&A, register to vote, more information, 2013 August 9
    - Join the 2013 Drone Summit!, 2013 August 9
    - TOP TEN REASONS TO ATTEND THE FONDA PEACE CONFERENCE Next Friday and Saturday, August 16th and 17th., 2013 August 10
    - Lynne Stewart still needs our help more than ever. Call and write to the Director of the Federal Bureau of Prisons. Time is of the essence., 2013 August 11
    - WAWaction edited and improved version: Lynne Stewart still needs our help more than ever. Call and write to the Director of the Federal Bureau of Prisons. Time is of the essence., 2013 August 11
    - Invitation to a BOOK DISCUSSION of Malalai Joya's "A Woman Among Warlords" Wednesday, September 18, 2013, 7 PM, Bethlehem Town Hall, Do you need a book? Are you intered in attending?, 2013 August 13
    - Doris and Donald Shaffer Memorial Lecture Series: "FROM NEIGHBORHOODS TO SETTLEMENTS" Tuesday, August 27, 4:00 to 7 PM Pittsfield MA Film, Forum and Speakers, 2013 August 18
    - CIA confirms role in 1953 Iran Coup! overthrowing democratically elected Prime Minister, Mohammed Mosaddeq, 2013 August 19
    - Another Chance to see the documentary film "The Throwaways!" Thursday, August 22, 7 PM at FUUSA, 405 Washington Avenue, Albany, 2013 August 20
    - Plans for Upstate New York to react to Sentencing Announcement for Bradley Manning tomorrow, 8/21 and Thursday, 8/22 in Syracuse., 2013 August 20
    - New blog article -- sort of a prayer for leniency in the sentencing of Bradley Manning, scheduled for 10 am tomorrow morning, 8/21, 2013 August 20
    - Malalai Joya and Eve Ensler issue a joint statement about the January 2012 rape and murder of a young Afghan woman by an as yet unpunished warlord., 2013 August 21
    - Albany Public Library Talk - a reminder - What's going on at UArdvark?, Tuesday, August 27, 12:15 PM, Albany Main Library., 2013 August 22
    - Great coverage of WAW's Iran Vigil at Food Fival, 2013 August 22
    - From Jewish Voice for Peace, 8,500 petition signatures to Kerry about stopping settlement expansion - we need yours!, 2013 August 23
    - October 10 through 19th Maine Anti Drone walk from Northern Maine to Bath with Code Pink and Veterans for Peace and Global Network Against Weapons and Nuclear Power in Space, 2013 August 24
    - POTUS logic re Syria, 2013 August 26
    - Syria: I just wrote President Obama " Will You? Good information about alternatives to military intervention, sample letter and le tter writing template from FCNL., 2013 August 27
    - Tell President Obama not to Attack Syria, 2013 August 27
    - UNAC, NO U.S. War on Syria. Is there inter in doing an action in Albany?, 2013 August 27
    - Fw: if only the people would use their power, 2013 August 28
    - Stop the War on Syria, 2013 August 28
    - CPD on Syria: Roundtable & Action, 2013 August 28
    - Stop the War on Syria- This is personal for me! Please show up!, 2013 August 28
    - Demonstration to Stop the War on Syria is THIS SATURDAY, AUGUST 31, 2013, 2013 August 29
    - Stop the War on Syria, 2013 August 30
    - You are invited to a Rally and March in Defense of Women's Rights, Saturday, September 7th at 1 PM, New Paltz Peace Park, 2013 August 31
    - Syria Vigil noon Wed. Sept. 4, 2013 September 1
    - Good coverage of Saturday Syria demonstrations - Urge Tonko, Gibson, Gillibrand & Schumer to oppose war, 2013 September 2
    - Updated flier for distribution - Help build Sept. 7 Women's Rights Rally and March, Saturday, September 7th at 1 PM, New Paltz Peace Park, 2013 September 2
    - Urge Tonko, Gibson, Gillibrand & Schumer to oppose war, call or email their local offices or their foreign policy aides (see Maud's email below), 2013 September 3
    - Re: WAWaction Urge Tonko, Gibson, Gillibrand & Schumer to oppose war, call or email their local offices or their foreign policy aides (see Maud's email below), 2013 September 3
    - If you're near White Plains NY, Emergency Prot Friday Sept. 6th, 5 PM against a military attack on Syria, 2013 September 3
    - Powerful story about a veteran with Traumatic Brain Injury, 2013 September 3
    - survey on Syria from Rep Gibson's office, 2013 September 4
    - Pause it! USA military attack against Syria, 2013 September 5
    - Fwd: 60 Hours Left Indiegogo fund raising for documentary, "The Hebron Story", 2013 September 5
    - Saturday, September 7th at 3 PM anti-war meeting to organize next steps in effort to prevent a US attack on Syria, 153 South Pearl Street, Albany, 2013 September 5
    - "Actions can speak Volumes" By Maureen Baillargeon Aumand, Commentary, Wednesday, September 4, 2013, 2013 September 5
    - Useful article about civil society in Syria, by Mel Duncan, 2013 September 6
    - A good petition from Representative Alan Grayson & A stop the war on Syria vigil with Bethelehem Neighbors for Peace on Monday, September 8th at 5 PM, 2013 September 6
    - Check out This Week's 'New York NOW' Poll Quion | New York NOW, 2013 September 6
    - Wonderful poetic story By Naomi Shihab Nye, published Sunday August 25, 2013, 2013 September 7
    - North Star Peace Walk September 15th at 2 PM, Starts at Congregation Beth Emeth Parking lot and ends at Masjid As Salaam, 2013 September 7
    - Call Representative Tonko's office early this week & Join a Vigil near you to oppose strikes on Syria, Mon. Sept. 9th & Links to some good articles for background info., 2013 September 8
    - New Barbara Lee Resolution for Diplomatic Solution to Syrian Crisis. Urge your Representative to sign on., 2013 September 9
    - Call Representative Tonko!, 2013 September 9
    - September 10th Conversation with Representative Paul Tonko's legislative aide Brendan Larkin this morning about where Rep. Tonko stands on authorizing military force against Syria, 2013 September 10
    - Afghan Activist Malalai Joya Coming Here!, 2013 September 11
    - Seize the moment! Petition to ask Presidnet Obama to meet with new Iranian President Hassan Rouhani at the UN General Assembly in October, 2013 September 11
    - Petition to Engage Iran for a ceasefire in Syria, 2013 September 12
    - WAWaction Petition to Engage Iran for a ceasefire in Syria, 2013 September 12
    - Reminder: Interfaith "North Star" Peace Walk Sunday, Sept. 15, 2 PM in Albany. Begins at the parking lot of Congregation Beth Emeth and ends at Masjid As-Salam, 2013 September 13
    - CODEPINK - Help an Iraqi single mom get justice!, 2013 September 15
    - Peace walk 9/22 initiated by Grafton Peace Pagoda in conjunction with the Saratoga Peace Fair, Sunday, September 22, 24 Circular Street, Saratoga Noon to 4 PM, 2013 September 16
    - 2013 Peace Fair Information, 2013 September 16
    - Correction of the Day for the Peace Fair on SUNDAY Septemberr 22, From Noon to 4 PM, 2013 September 17
    - Just in case you forgot! Book Discussion of Malalai Joya's autobiography "A Woman Among Warlords" Wednesday evening 9/18, 7 PM Bethlehem Town Hall, 2013 September 17
    - Showing of the film "Afghan Women: A History of Struggle" Monday, September 30, 7 PM Women's Club of Albany, discussion by photojournalist Connie Frisbee Houde, 2013 September 18
    - Peace Action Fund of New York Event honoring Medea Benjamin Monday, Oct. 28 in NYC, Carpooling available, 2013 September 18
    - An invitation to the Solidarity 30th Anniversary Celebration dinner, Saturday, October 19th from 3 PM to 7 PM, FUUSA, Albany, featured speaker Chris Townsend, 2013 September 20
    - Fwd: Baby stuff needed right away! Can you help this Emmaus Hou, 2013 September 21
    - In New York City, Free Outdoor film screening ' In search of prisoner 650 The story of Aafia Siddiqui, Monday, September 23, 7:30 PM to 10 PM, Diversity Plaza, Jackson Heights, Queens, 2013 September 22
    - Here are Three Ways [Rally, Sign the new petition, Send a birth, 2013 September 22
    - Here are Three Ways [Rally, Sign the new petition, Send a birthday card or note] that you can wish Political prisoner and civil rights lawyer Lynne Stewart a Happier 74th birthday on October 8th. Let"s Bring her Home!, 2013 September 22
    - Reminder: Kurdish Quion & Syria, Talk at the Turkish Cultural Center, Albany, Vera Eccarius-Kelly, Political Science Professor at Siena, Thursday, September 26th 6:30 PM-8:30 PM, 2013 September 24
    - Fwd: House passes Monsanto Protection Act, 2013 September 24
    - [TONIGHT] Tell Randolph County NC school board to reverse its ban on "Invisible Man", 2013 September 25
    - Fw: Support the Albany Common Council Resolution Against The NDAA, 2013 September 26
    - Fw: REMINDER: Showing of the film "Afghan Women: A History of Struggle" Monday, September 30, 7 PM Women's Club of Albany, discussion by photojournalist Connie Frisbee Houde, 2013 September 26
    - Invitation to Corruption conference @ The New School, NYC, Nov 21-22, 2013 September 26
    - Voices of Syrian women in civil resistance an article by Nada Alwadi, 2013 September 29
    - Rally for Lynne Stewart - Tuesday, October 8 at Noon, Leo O'Brien Federal Building, 1 Clinton Avenue, Albany, 2013 September 30
    - Make Plans to hear Afghan activist and young leader, Malalai Joya speak on Wednesday October 9th in two locations (afternoon and evening)., 2013 September 30
    - REMINDER: Performance of Hit-Play "Mercy Killers" - Thurs. Oct. 3rd 7:00 - 9:00 pm at Steamer #10 theatre in Albany, 2013 October 1
    - WAMC/JStreet Film: State 194 Thursday, Oct 10, 7 PM About Paline becoming the 194th State recognized by the UN, 2013 October 1
    - Malalai Joya on "Democracy Now!" tomorrow (Thursday, October 3rd) She has arrived safely in the US on Tuesday night and will begin a series of talks in NYC and then in Mass before coming here on October 9th., 2013 October 2
    - On Oct. 29th Maureen Aumand, Kathy Manley,and the Sanctuary for Independent Media honored by The Tom Paine Chapter of Veterans for Peace, in Latham, 2013 October 2
    - Requ from Russell Sage Afghan student, Yagana Hafed, for funding help with an LSAT preparation class, from Connie Frisbee Houde, 2013 October 4
    - Special Parking info for Malalai Joya event at FUUSA Wed Oct 9, 7 PM, and don't forget her talk at Sage College in Troy at 1 PM also on October 9th., 2013 October 4
    - Please join Grannies for Peace Vigil to Prot Drones, 2013 October 5
    - Personal response to spending time with Malalai Joya and final reminder that she will be speaking in the Capital District on Wednesday, October 9th, 2013 October 6
    - Lynne Stewart October 8 at noon Albany, At the federal building, invitation to a sign making party, Monday, October 7th, and an op-ed written by Kathy Manley and Steve Downs in Friday's TU, 2013 October 6
    - Reminder: Rally for Lynne Stewart October 8 at noon Albany, 2013 October 7
    - Workshop for Anti-Drones Activists with Rafia Zakaria: Oct 23, 7 PM, 2013 October 8
    - Fwd: (muslim_solidarity) Albany, NY passes resolution opposing indefinite detention in the NDAA, 2013 October 8
    - WAW Annual Awards Dinner & Silent Auction SAVE THE DATE!, 2013 October 9
    - Thursday, October 24, Exhibit 6-9 PM Program 7 PM, "Humor from my Pen" political cartoons by Gerardo Hernandez, on of the Cuban 5 political prisoners, FUUSA., 2013 October 10
    - Great article in today's TU about Malalai, 2013 October 10
    - Using Social Media for Social Change, 10/26, 2013 October 11
    - Fw: On the anniversary of his murder, demand justice for Alex Odeh, 2013 October 11
    - You are Invited!!! Join Prisoners' Legal Services as it Celebrates National Pro Bono Week - October 21st, 2013 October 14
    - Fw: Reservation Deadline October 16 for Premier of the film "12 years a Slave" at the Spectrum Theatre on Monday October 21st., 2013 October 15
    - Save the date for Women Against War's Annual Meeting - Thurs, Nov 14, 2013 5:30 PM, 2013 October 15
    - Reminder that all are invited to Anti Drone Vigil Thursday, October 17th Noon to 1 PM, Corner of Wolf Road and Central Avenue, Albany. Some signs and banners provided., 2013 October 15
    - volunteer web coordinator needed; position available, 2013 October 15
    - UAlbany Peace Action Speakout against Gun Violence, Thursday October 24th at 11 am, Uptown campus, 2013 October 16
    - Monday, Oct. 28, 7 PM program on work in Nicaragua by ecumenical group, CEPAD, First United Methodist Church, Schenectady, 2013 October 17
    - Time is Short Please RSVP for the VFP Awards Dinner on October 29th, by October 21st., 2013 October 19
    - Fw: A new course - Nonviolent Struggle - Theory and Practice, 2013 October 19
    - Oct. 23 Please Come Thanks Maude Easter, 2013 October 21
    - This week: Albany and Troy, Oct 23 &24, 2013 WAW speaker Pakistani-American Journalist Rafia Zakaria, 2013 October 21
    - This Week-- Women Writers of the Middle East at UAlbany, free and open to the public, 2013 October 21
    - Press Release for Thrusday Drone Action Trial - Please Share, 2013 October 22
    - Great story on Rafia Zakaria's talk at SUNY, 2013 October 24
    - Nominate a Fabulous Feminist! Deadline is October 25th!, 2013 October 24
    - HISTORIC ACQUITTAL OF ANTI-DRONE ACTIVISTS AT HANCOCK AIR BASE (including our own Steering Committee Member, Linda LeTendre), 2013 October 25
    - Another great article on Rafia Zakaria's visit!, 2013 October 25
    - For a limited time only you can watch this full 26 minute documentary "Wounds of Waziristan" It's very powerful and appropriate to what Pakistani journalist and human rights advocate Rafia Zakaria has discussed., 2013 October 27
    - Here's the link to an article by Mabel Leon about the October 17th drone demonstration, featuring Mabel's photos and a couple of "Peace Now" video interviews by Trudy Quaif, 2013 October 28
    - TUESDAY, 10/29, history will be made - drone survivors speak with Congress 10 am to 11am (live streaming), 2013 October 28
    - I just signed End LGBTQ discrimination by religious groups, 2013 October 29
    - W: [undergroundrailroad] Two Events of Inter on November 2, 2013 Private Screening and discussion of 12 Years a Slave, 9 am and Anti-Racism Workshop 9am to 3:30 PM, 2013 October 30
    - Rashid Khalidi speaks on the Middle East, Thurs, Nov 21, 2013, 2013 October 30
    - [tianys] Ahmadiyya Muslim Community Dinner Event Date and Time changed to Sunday, November 17th 6:00-7:30 pm. RSVP addresses and schedule, 2013 October 31
    - Intering presentation on PTSD and vets' issues, 2013 October 31
    - Wednesday, November 13, 7 PM to 8:45 PM, Paul Rehm and Alice Brody on Israel/Paline:Children and the Face of Occupation, Bethlehem Public Library, 2013 November 3
    - [undergroundrailroad] "Slavery by Another Name" Film and discussion, Wednesday, November 6th 7 PM to 9 PM, Siena College, 2013 November 4
    - Fwd: (muslim_solidarity) Fw: [UNAC-discussion] Thanksgiving Letter from Lynne Stewart, 2013 November 4
    - New Facebook Link to Rashid Khalidi Event, Nov. 21st, 2013 November 4
    - [PakistanTrip] Drone lawyer for head of WHAT?!, 2013 November 7
    - You're Invited! ALL ARE WELCOME!!!, 2013 November 7
    - Your feminist peace group needs your help!, 2013 November 8
    - Black Friday prot!, 2013 November 8
    - Upcoming event at HVCC, Tuesday, November 12th, 11 am, Dr. Allison Stokes "Learning about Islam and Reaching across Faith Divides", 2013 November 9
    - We have until tomorrow night to sign petitions to the Israeli Knesset to stop the forced eviction of more than 40,000 Arab Bedouin's from their ancral homes to make way for Jewish settlements., 2013 November 10
    - Photos from a Bedouin Village on the outskirts of Jericho, taken by Alice Brody, 2013 November 10
    - Wednesday, 11/13, 7 PM Israel/Paline, Children and the Face of Occupation. Thursday 11/14, begins at 5:30 PM, Women Against War annual meeting, potluck, Rachel Smolker, Honoring Pat Beetle as Woman of Peac, 2013 November 11
    - WAW Steering Committee Nominated Members, 2013 November 11
    - Reminder -Thurs, Nov 14: Come Honor Pat Beetle & Hear Climate Justice Activist Rachel Smolker, 2013 November 11
    - You are Invited to Saratoga Co. LWV Program Wed., Nov 20, 2013, 7 PM, 2013 November 12
    - Free Workshop at UAlbany, downtown Campus, "Children w/ Incarcerated Parents"- Nov.18th 1:30 PM to 5 PM Page Auditorium. Pre-Registration required, see below., 2013 November 13
    - Correction and reminder, WAW Annual Meeting Location, 2013 November 13
    - Wednesday, November 20, 7 PM College of St. Rose - Thursday, November 21, UAlbany, 3 PM- Two Chances to hear Cuban Professor Dr. Evarina Deulofeu speak about Progress Toward Equality: Lessons From Cuba's Struggle Against Racism, Sexism and Homophobia., 2013 November 13
    - Local showing of "Unmanned: America's Drone Wars" Tuesday 11/ 19, 7 PM, Bethlehemen Town Hall. 1 hour documentary by Robert Greenwald with discussion to follow, and links to 2 blog articles about drone strikes in Pakistan, 2013 November 15